# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)



hunt_red_october = Movie.create(title: 'The Hunt For Red October');

hunt_red_october_quiz_1 = hunt_red_october.quizzes.create(title: 'Hunt For Red October Quiz 1');


hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 1, question: "'The Hunt for Red October' is a movie about a submarine from what country?", answer_option_a: 'Canada', answer_option_b: 'China', answer_option_c: 'Germany', answer_option_d: 'Russia', correct_answer: 'Russia', answer_context: "It is of course about a Russian submarine, or as it was when the movie was released, a Soviet submarine, since the country was still called the Soviet Union.");
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 2, question: "Which actor does NOT appear in 'The Hunt for Red October'?", answer_option_a: 'James Earl Jones', answer_option_b: 'Alec Baldwin', answer_option_c: 'Sean Connery', answer_option_d: 'Tommy Lee Jones', correct_answer: 'Tommy Lee Jones', answer_context: "James Earl Jones, the voice of Darth Vader, is of course in this movie, as are Sean Connery and Alec Baldwin. Jones and Baldwin are American, while Connery plays the Russian submarine captain"); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 3, question: "When does the story in the movie take place?", answer_option_a: '1970s', answer_option_b: '1990s', answer_option_c: '1980s', answer_option_d: '1940s', correct_answer: '1980s', answer_context: "The movie plot takes place during 1984. Actual release of the film was not done until 1989, but since the movie was based upon a book, written by Tom Clancy, he wrote the story, which took place in 1984 in the book.");
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 4, question: "One of the names of the United States' submarines in the movie was USS 'Dallas'. Is there a real submarine with this name?", answer_option_a: 'Yes', answer_option_b: 'No', answer_option_c: '', answer_option_d: '', correct_answer: 'Yes', answer_context: "The USS 'Dallas' is a real submarine."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 5, question: "In the movie, there is an area of underwater canyons that the submarine 'Red October' uses to hide in and head across the Atlantic ocean. What do the American's call this route?", answer_option_a: ' passage to the deep', answer_option_b: 'canyon ball run', answer_option_c: 'red route one', answer_option_d: 'the double peaks', correct_answer: 'red route one', answer_context: "The Americans aboard the USS 'Dallas' submarine call this passage Red Route One, and they know that the Russians have very accurate maps of this area, so they don't try to follow them in there."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 6, question: "What is the name of the secret drive aboard the 'Red October' submarine that allows them to run very quiet in the water?", answer_option_a: 'Secret Drive', answer_option_b: 'Caterpillar Drive', answer_option_c: 'Magneto-prop Drive', answer_option_d: 'Torpedo Drive', correct_answer: 'Caterpillar Drive', answer_context: "It was called a caterpillar drive, and it has no moving parts so it allows the submarine to move very quickly through the water."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 7, question: "What do the Americans say the secret drive of the 'Red October' would sound like if they could hear it with their sonar?", answer_option_a: 'Magma Bubbling', answer_option_b: 'Whales Humping', answer_option_c: 'Sonic Reverberation', answer_option_d: 'Fujito Magneto Holycowito', correct_answer: 'Whales Humping', answer_context: "Well they say it would sound like whales humping or some seismic anomaly; anything but a submarine. The computer on the USS 'Dallas' thinks it is a Magma Displacement, but the people never think that it is that."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 8, question: "Who was the captain of the submarine 'Red October'?", answer_option_a: 'Capt. Burt Mancuso', answer_option_b: 'Capt. Jack Ryan', answer_option_c: 'Capt. Vasili Borodin', answer_option_d: 'Capt. Marko Ramius', correct_answer: 'Capt. Marko Ramius', answer_context: "While all of the names were actual captains in the movie, except Dr. Jack Ryan, he is a Ph.D., not a captain. Capt. Mancuso was captain of the USS 'Dallas', and Capt. Borodin was actually second in command of the 'Red October'."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 9, question: "In the movie the American sonar man on the USS 'Dallas' refers to a 'crazy Ivan' while following the submarine 'Red October'. What is a 'crazy Ivan'?", answer_option_a: 'Depth charges in the water', answer_option_b: 'A sudden turn by a submarine', answer_option_c: 'Torpedo!', answer_option_d: 'The name of the chef on the submarine', correct_answer: 'A sudden turn by a submarine', answer_context: "It is of course meant to indicate that the Russian submarine has made a sudden, unexpected turn. It is done to check to see if anyone is behind the Russian submarine. The only way to avoid detection is to go dead silent and make like a hole in the water."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 10, question: "At the end of the movie 'The Hunt for Red October' where are the Americans trying to hide the submarine 'Red October'?", answer_option_a: 'Maine, USA', answer_option_b: 'Florida, USA', answer_option_c: 'Labrador, Canada', answer_option_d: 'Cuba', correct_answer: 'Maine, USA', answer_context: "They are trying to hide the submarine in a river in Maine so that the Russian satellites will not detect it, because it is not near any military bases."); 

hunt_red_october_quiz_2 = hunt_red_october.quizzes.create(title: 'Hunt For Red October Quiz 2');

hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 1, question: "What city does Jack Ryan live in?", answer_option_a: 'Paris', answer_option_b: 'Frankfurt', answer_option_c: 'New York', answer_option_d: 'London', correct_answer: 'London', answer_context: "He starts out leaving from Heathrow Airport.");
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 2, question: "What military position did James Earl Jones' character hold prior to retirement?", answer_option_a: 'Secretary of Defense', answer_option_b: 'USN Admiral', answer_option_c: 'Secretary of State', answer_option_d: 'Chairman of the Joint Chiefs', correct_answer: 'USN Admiral', answer_context: "He was a United States Navy Admiral."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 3, question: "What is the name of Jack Ryan's daughter's teddy bear?", answer_option_a: 'Paddington', answer_option_b: 'Stanley', answer_option_c: 'Barkley', answer_option_d: 'Pooh', correct_answer: 'Stanley', answer_context: "The bears name was Stanley");
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 4, question: "What about flying does Ryan not like?", answer_option_a: 'Taking off', answer_option_b: 'Turbulence', answer_option_c: 'Tight spaces', answer_option_d: 'Landing', correct_answer: 'Turbulence', answer_context: "Ryan describes turbulence as the reason he can't sleep on airplanes."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 5, question: "What was Captain Raimius's nickname in the USSR?", answer_option_a: 'The Vilnius Schoolmaster', answer_option_b: 'The Soviet Skipper', answer_option_c: 'The Russian Regent', answer_option_d: 'The Moscow Mariner', correct_answer: 'The Vilnius Schoolmaster', answer_context: "Captain Raimius trained most of the sub captains in the Russian navy, and was known as the Vilnius Schoolmaster"); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 6, question: "What state did the second-in-command on the Red October want to see more than anything?", answer_option_a: 'Montana', answer_option_b: 'Texas', answer_option_c: 'California', answer_option_d: 'Florida', correct_answer: 'Montana', answer_context: "He would really like to see Montana"); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 7, question: "What was the doctor's name on the Red October?", answer_option_a: 'Petrov', answer_option_b: 'Pershiv', answer_option_c: 'Strangelove', answer_option_d: 'Petrius', correct_answer: 'Petrov', answer_context: "He was played by Tim Curry!"); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 8, question: "What was the name of the American sub that Ryan boarded?", answer_option_a: 'USS Dallas', answer_option_b: 'USS Nashville', answer_option_c: 'USS Enterprise', answer_option_d: 'SSN Indianapolis', correct_answer: 'USS Dallas', answer_context: "The American sub Jack Ryan boarded was the USS Dallas, which is a real American submarine."); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 9, question: "Who was the subject of the book Jack Ryan wrote that Capt. Raimius had read?", answer_option_a: 'Admiral Halsey', answer_option_b: 'Admiral Nimitz', answer_option_c: 'Admiral John Paul Jones', answer_option_d: 'Admiral Spitz', correct_answer: 'Admiral Halsey', answer_context: "'I know this book. Your conclusions were all wrong, Ryan. Halsey acted stupidly.'"); 
hunt_red_october_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 10, question: "Who was the captain of the Soviet submarine whom Raimius had trained and who was hunting the Red October?", answer_option_a: 'Vilnius', answer_option_b: 'Tupelov', answer_option_c: 'Pedori', answer_option_d: 'Gregari', correct_answer: 'Tupelov', answer_context: "Tupelov was a former student of Raimius, who according to rumors, had a special place in his heart for Raimius."); 

dune = Movie.create(title: 'Dune');

dune_quiz_1 = dune.quizzes.create(title: 'Dune Quiz 1');

dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 1, question: "The first face one sees in 'Dune' is that of Princess Irulan, daughter of the emperor of the known universe. What actress portrays Irulan, seen before the credits as the film's narrator?", answer_option_a: 'Sissy Spacek', answer_option_b: 'Demi Moore', answer_option_c: 'Virginia Madsen', answer_option_d: 'Holly Hunter', correct_answer: 'Virginia Madsen', answer_context: "Virginia Madsen, famous for her roles in 'The Rainmaker' and 'Sideways', appears as the very young Princess Irulan in 'Dune'. Though she did not have many lines within the film, she did get plenty of talking time as the narrator. This was only Madsen's third film!");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 2, question: "During the opening narration, we learn a bit about the history of the known universe. Particularly, it is pointed out that one planet has grown in importance due to its production of an all-important spice. This planet is called 'Dune', or alternatively, what?", answer_option_a: 'Kwisatz', answer_option_b: 'Arrakis', answer_option_c: 'Ramallo', answer_option_d: 'Halleck', correct_answer: 'Arrakis', answer_context: "Arrakis is actually the true name of the planet, it is only known colloquially as Dune (based on the fact that the entire planet is a desert). The name 'Arrakis' was derived by 'Dune' author Frank Herbert from the Arabic word for 'dancer'");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 3, question: "During the credits, we discover all those who have been involved in the creation of 'Dune'. What popular rock group from the 1980s was responsible for the soundtrack for the film", answer_option_a: 'The Fixx', answer_option_b: 'Loverboy', answer_option_c: 'Toto', answer_option_d: 'The Police', correct_answer: 'Toto', answer_context: "Toto, famous for hits such as 'Africa' and 'Rosanna', lent their musical expertise to the film, and to great effect. They also performed the 'Prophecy Theme', which was composed by Brian Eno, the 'Father of Ambient Music'.");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 4, question: "In a secret report from the Spacing Guild, we are introduced to some of the other important planets in the known universe. Among them is a lush, green-hued planet, largely covered in water, that is home to the House Atreides. What is this pleasant orb called?", answer_option_a: 'Orcadia', answer_option_b: 'Hesperian', answer_option_c: 'Jovania', answer_option_d: 'Caladan', correct_answer: 'Caladan', answer_context: "Caladan is the birthplace of Paul Atreides, the main character of our story. Having grown up on Caladan, he is about to embark on an adventure that will see his entire life change!");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 5, question: "What makes the planet Kaitan, home of the emperor of the known universe, unique from the other planets introduced at the early juncture in the film?", answer_option_a: 'It is a frozen planet.', answer_option_b: 'It appears to be entirely black.', answer_option_c: 'It has rings.', answer_option_d: 'It appears to have a great deal of volcanic activity.', correct_answer: 'It has rings.', answer_context: "Kaitain, a ringed planet, appears to be very much Earth-like in its composition, with clouds and lush greens and blue hues. However, we never really get to see much of Kaitain in the film.");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 6, question: "In the first scene of the film, the emperor of the known universe, namely Shaddam Corrino IV, is confronted by a third stage Space Guild navigator about his plans regarding the houses of Atreides and Harkonnen. What able, classic Hollywood actor portrays Shaddam IV in this film?", answer_option_a: 'Anthony Quinn', answer_option_b: 'Jose Ferrer', answer_option_c: 'Glenn Ford', answer_option_d: 'Burt Lancaster', correct_answer: 'Jose Ferrer', answer_context: "José Ferrer, who appeared in films such as 'The Caine Mutiny' and 'Lawrence of Arabia', helps launch the film in style with his powerful acting style.");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 7, question: "During the conversation between the Emperor and the navigator from the Space Guild, it is requested that the Emperor's confidant, one Reverend Mother Gaius Helen Mohiam, leave the premises. Of what powerful religious organization is she a part?", answer_option_a: 'Bene Gesserit', answer_option_b: 'Lost Tleilaxu', answer_option_c: 'Shadout Mapes', answer_option_d: 'The Echorium', correct_answer: 'Bene Gesserit', answer_context: "Bene Gesserit is a name derived from the Latin for 'she shall have behaved well', which is ironic because the Reverend Mother seems to behave pretty badly in this film! The Bene Gesserit is a long-lived sisterhood of witches who have learned to control their own bodies and minds, and can control the bodies and minds of others.");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 8, question: "The Emperor seems to be concerned with the growing popularity of the leader of the House of Atreides, namely Duke Leto Atreides. What marvelous German actor portrays the Duke in 'Dune'?", answer_option_a: 'Jugen Prochnow', answer_option_b: 'Wolf Kahler', answer_option_c: 'Ernst Bader', answer_option_d: 'Rudiger Vogler', correct_answer: 'Jugen Prochnow', answer_context: "Jürgen Prochnow is a very recognizable face, having appeared in such films as 'Das Boot', 'The English Patient' and 'Air Force One', among many others. He also portrayed the key villain, Max Dent, in the Eddie Murphy movie 'Beverly Hills Cop II'.");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 9, question: "What is the name of the assembly of noble houses within which Duke Atreides popularity has been rising?", answer_option_a: 'Althing', answer_option_b: 'Bundesraad', answer_option_c: 'Landsraad', answer_option_d: 'Stording', correct_answer: 'Landsraad', answer_context: "Landsraad is a word from the Danish, where it means 'regional council'. Herbert clearly didn't mind borrowing terms from multiple languages! The Landsraad contains representatives from all the major houses, including Atreides and Harkonnen.");
dune_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 10, question: "During the Emperor's conversation with the navigator from the Space Guild, he learns that the organization wants a certain member of the House of Atreides killed. Who would this be?", answer_option_a: 'Lady Jessica', answer_option_b: 'Duke Leto Atreides', answer_option_c: 'Paul Atreides', answer_option_d: 'Alia Atreides', correct_answer: 'Paul Atreides', answer_context: "When the navigator suggests that Paul Atreides is a danger, the Emperor at first believes him to have misspoken, after all, Paul is just a boy. The navigator then makes it very clear that it is indeed Paul who is a danger to the current order in the universe, and that the Spice Guild wants him killed. Soon we will discover why!");

dune_quiz_2 = dune.quizzes.create(title: 'Dune Quiz 2');

dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 1, question: "There is talk of a messiah-like figure amongst several of the characters, and some suspect that Paul might very well be this 'Kwisatz Haderach'. What other term is used to describe this very powerful individual?", answer_option_a: 'Prodigal-man', answer_option_b: 'Preponderant', answer_option_c: 'Ubergenius', answer_option_d: 'Superbeing', correct_answer: 'Superbeing', answer_context: "The 'Kwisatz Haderach' (a name that means 'Shortening of the Way') is a prophecied male superbeing that could tell the future, and even manipulate it. The Bene Gesserit Sisterhood has been manipulating bloodlines for 90 generations to produce this superbeing...and the prophecy is about to be fulfilled!");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 2, question: "What is the name of the beautiful, bound concubine of Duke Leto Atreides, herself a member of the Bene Gesserit Sisterhood?", answer_option_a: 'Lady Amanda', answer_option_b: 'Lady Jessica', answer_option_c: 'Lady Pauline', answer_option_d: 'Lady Ophelia', correct_answer: 'Lady Jessica', answer_context: "The lovely Lady Jessica is played in this film by English actress Francesca Annis. Annis has been acting since 1958, she was a child actress at that point. She has appeared in a great many other films besides 'Dune', including 'Cleopatra', 'Krull' and 'The Libertine'.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 3, question: "When we first see him, Paul Atreides is sitting at his desk, studying the current situation in the universe with great interest. He reviews some facts, including one about a race of 'human computers' with red-stained lips. What are these individuals called??", answer_option_a: 'Genii', answer_option_b: 'Mentats', answer_option_c: 'Cerebrates', answer_option_d: 'Laureates', correct_answer: 'Mentats', answer_context: "The Mentat order was established long ago when machines with artificial intelligence could no longer be trusted. Thufir Hawat is the most prominent example of a Mentat in this film, with Piter de Vries also representing the order, though he is a 'twisted Mentat'. The red-stained lips of the Mentats are caused by the ingestion of sapho juice, a substance that amplifies their mental powers.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 4, question: "While Paul studies in his personal chamber, three men approach him from behind. Which of these is not one of them?", answer_option_a: 'Doctor Yueh', answer_option_b: 'Gurney Halleck', answer_option_c: 'Thufir Hawat', answer_option_d: 'Duncan Idaho', correct_answer: 'Duncan Idaho', answer_context: "These three men have clearly been intimately involved in Paul's upbringing, and he seems to have a close relationship with each of them. In particular, Gurney and Paul have a camaraderie that is clearly exhibited in the film.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 5, question: "Several important minor characters are fleshed out during the early scenes of this film. One of them is Gurney Halleck, skilled soldier and loyal friend of the House of Atreides. What then little-known actor portrayed Gurney in 'Dune'?", answer_option_a: 'Ian McKellen', answer_option_b: 'Ted Danson', answer_option_c: 'George Clooney', answer_option_d: 'Patrick Stewart', correct_answer: 'Patrick Stewart', answer_context: "Patrick Stewart, best known for his role as Captain Jean-Luc Picard from the 'Star Trek: The Next Generation' television show and films, shows off his acting talents, even in this minor role. Stewart appeared in several sci-fi/fantasy films of the early 80s, including 'Excalibur' and 'Lifeforce' before hitting it big with his 'Star Trek' gig!");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 6, question: "Doctor Yueh is another of the close confidants of the Atreides family. What interesting character actor, appearing in several of David Lynch's films, takes on this challenging role?", answer_option_a: 'Anthony Hopkins', answer_option_b: 'Dennis Hopper', answer_option_c: 'Dean Stockwell', answer_option_d: 'John Hurt', correct_answer: 'Dean Stockwell', answer_context: "Dean Stockwell is an interesting Hollywood personality, having been a child actor beginning in 1945 with his appearances in films such as 'The Valley of Decision' and 'Anchors Away'. After doing a bunch of bit roles on TV and in films during the 1960s and 1970s, Stockwell seemed to have been rediscovered in the 1980s, and went on to appear in a lot of great 80s movies, not to mention the television show 'Quantum Leap'.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 7, question: "During the scenes in the House of Atreides, we first learn the name of the all-important spice that everyone is fussing about. What is the term for this powerful, life-expanding substance?", answer_option_a: 'Negus', answer_option_b: 'Tikka', answer_option_c: 'Masala', answer_option_d: 'Melange', correct_answer: 'Melange', answer_context: "Melange seems to be more than just life-expanding, it's also a very addictive and has psychotropic powers. Melange can only be found on one planet, Arakkis (aka Dune), thus why there is so much contention amongst the powerful families of the Landsraad.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 8, question: "In an early scene, Paul is pitted against a 'fighter', a deadly machine with multiple, extending weapons. This is no challenge for Paul, however, who uses an interesting martial art that involves the power of sound. What is the term for this fighting technique?", answer_option_a: 'Animating', answer_option_b: 'Visitating', answer_option_c: 'Invcating', answer_option_d: 'Weirding', correct_answer: 'Weirding', answer_context: "The Weirding Way has been cultivated over many generations by the Bene Gesserit, and Paul seems to have the gift almost naturally. In the film, the Weirding is focused through hand-held modules that help amplify sound. Paul uses just such a module against the fighter.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 9, question: "The House of Atreides has been summoned to take power on the Planet Dune, replacing the Harkonnens. Sensing a trap, Duke Leto Atreides sends some of his best troops ahead as a security measure. What loyal friend of the House of Atreides is sent ahead to oversee security on Dune?", answer_option_a: 'Piter De Vries', answer_option_b: 'Dr. Kynes', answer_option_c: 'Stilgar', answer_option_d: 'Duncan Idaho', correct_answer: 'Duncan Idaho', answer_context: "In 'Dune', the short-lived Duncan Idaho is portrayed by actor Richard Jordan, who also appeared in such films as 'The Yakuza', 'Logan's Run' and 'Raise the Titanic'.");
dune_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 10, question: "In a very intimate and philosophical conversation, which character utters the line, 'The sleeper must awaken' to Paul Atreides?", answer_option_a: 'Duke Leto Atreides', answer_option_b: 'Shadout Mapes', answer_option_c: 'Doctor Yueh', answer_option_d: 'Gurney Halleck', correct_answer: 'Duke Leto Atreides', answer_context: "Duke Leto, with my favorite lines in the film: 'I'll miss the sea, but a person needs new experiences. They jar something deep inside, allowing him to grow. Without change something sleeps inside us, and seldom awakens. The sleeper must awaken.'");

shawshank = Movie.create(title: 'Shawshank Redemption');

shawshank_quiz_1 = shawshank.quizzes.create(title: 'Shawshank Redemption Quiz 1');

shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 1, question: "What does Red call Andy when he first sees him get off the bus?", answer_option_a: 'Tall drink of water', answer_option_b: 'Tall timber', answer_option_c: 'Streak of pelican poo', answer_option_d: 'Skyscraper', correct_answer: 'Tall drink of water', answer_context: "Red goes on to bet for Andy but loses.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 2, question: "What is the collective name for the people who take a liking to Andy?", answer_option_a: 'The sisters', answer_option_b: 'The gays', answer_option_c: 'The brothers', answer_option_d: 'The nuns', correct_answer: 'The sisters', answer_context: "Thank God Boggs got his head punched in.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 3, question: "Where did Andy work before he went to prison?", answer_option_a: 'Bank', answer_option_b: 'Country Club', answer_option_c: 'Real Estate', answer_option_d: 'Stock Market', correct_answer: 'Bank', answer_context: "Andy was a hot shot banker.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 4, question: "What was Red's real name?", answer_option_a: 'Ellis Redding', answer_option_b: 'Red Elias', answer_option_c: 'Red Ellis', answer_option_d: 'Elias Redding', correct_answer: 'Ellis Redding', answer_context: "Hence his nickname 'Red'.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 5, question: "What is it that all people in Shawshank say they are?", answer_option_a: 'Cons', answer_option_b: 'Political Prisoners', answer_option_c: 'Innocent', answer_option_d: 'Saints', correct_answer: 'Innocent', answer_context: "Everyone except for Red, who admits he was guilty.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 6, question: "Where did Andy chuck the gun after he decided not to confront his wife and her lover?", answer_option_a: 'In the lake', answer_option_b: 'In the river', answer_option_c: 'In the trash', answer_option_d: 'In the prison', correct_answer: 'In the river', answer_context: "But unfortunately for Andy the gun was never found.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 7, question: "Did you ever find out if Andy may have been innocent?", answer_option_a: 'Yes', answer_option_b: 'No', answer_option_c: 'Maybe', answer_option_d: 'Bullwinkle', correct_answer: 'Yes', answer_context: "Yes, but the warden had the prisoner who knew the truth killed.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 8, question: "How long was the length of rope Andy got off one of the other prisoners?", answer_option_a: '5 feet', answer_option_b: '5 metres', answer_option_c: '6 metres', answer_option_d: '6 feet', correct_answer: '6 feet', answer_context: "They thought Andy was going to hang himself. But of course he didn't.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 9, question: "Who plays Andy?", answer_option_a: 'Morgan Freeman', answer_option_b: 'Tim Burton', answer_option_c: 'Tom Robbins', answer_option_d: 'Tim Robbins', correct_answer: 'Tim Robbins', answer_context: "Probably one of Tim Robbins' best roles.");
shawshank_quiz_1.questions.create(question_number: 10, question: "After Andy escaped did Red and Andy ever see each other again?", answer_option_a: 'No', answer_option_b: 'Maybe', answer_option_c: 'Yes', answer_option_d: 'Pickles', correct_answer: 'Yes', answer_context: "They sure did, right at the end of the movie, on the beach in Mexico.");

shawshank_quiz_2 = shawshank.quizzes.create(title: 'Shawshank Redemption Quiz 2');

shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 1, question: "The movie 'Shawshank Redemption' is based on what short story?", answer_option_a: 'Rita Hayworth and Shawshank Redemption', answer_option_b: 'Red and Andy', answer_option_c: 'The Shawshank Redemption', answer_option_d: 'The Prisoners of Shawshank', correct_answer: 'Rita Hayworth and Shawshank Redemption', answer_context: "The movie was based on a short story novel written by horror author Stephen King!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 2, question: "'Shawshank Redemption' was directed by what director?", answer_option_a: 'Andy Darabont', answer_option_b: 'Frank Darabont', answer_option_c: 'David Lester', answer_option_d: 'Stephen King', correct_answer: 'Frank Darabont', answer_context: "Shawshank was directed by Darabont, director of the recent 'Green Mile'!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 3, question: "The name of the prison in the movie is:", answer_option_a: 'Shawshank Local Prison', answer_option_b: 'Shawshank State Prison', answer_option_c: 'Shawshank Jail', answer_option_d: 'Shawshank County Jail', correct_answer: 'Shawshank State Prison', answer_context: "The outdoor prison scenes in the movie were actually shot at a reformatory in Mansfield, Ohio.");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 4, question: "Who bets that Andy will be the first person to crack on his first night in prison?", answer_option_a: 'Red', answer_option_b: 'Brooks', answer_option_c: 'Haywood', answer_option_d: 'Lloyd', correct_answer: 'Red', answer_context: "Red bets against Andy in the beginning of the movie, losing, of course!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 5, question: "Who is on the second girlie poster that Andy hangs in his prison cell?", answer_option_a: 'Greta Garbo', answer_option_b: 'Raquel Welch', answer_option_c: 'Marilyn Monroe', answer_option_d: 'Rita Hayworth', correct_answer: 'Marilyn Monroe', answer_context: "The poster was given to Andy by Red for his tenth anniversary in prison!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 6, question: "What does Andy give to Red as a gift after being rejected for parole?", answer_option_a: 'Bottle of Liquor', answer_option_b: 'Poster', answer_option_c: 'Harmonica', answer_option_d: 'Pack of Cigarettes', correct_answer: 'Harmonica', answer_context: "Andy went through one of Reds' competitors to give him the harmonica!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 7, question: "Brooks' character was played by whom?", answer_option_a: 'Morgan Freeman', answer_option_b: 'Gil Bellows', answer_option_c: 'William Sadler', answer_option_d: 'James Whitmore', correct_answer: 'James Whitmore', answer_context: "The character Brooks was played by James Whitmore!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 8, question: "The place Andy tells Red to go 'if you ever get out of here' (where Andy proposed) looks like something out of a what?", answer_option_a: 'Edgar Allan Poe poem', answer_option_b: 'beautiful sunset', answer_option_c: 'Stephen King book', answer_option_d: 'Robert Frost poem', correct_answer: 'Robert Frost poem', answer_context: "When Andy spoke to Red he told him to go to a field near Buxton that looks like something out of a Robert Frost poem!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 9, question: "Where was the field Andy told Red to go if he ever got out of there?", answer_option_a: 'Lexington', answer_option_b: 'Button', answer_option_c: 'Ruxton', answer_option_d: 'Buxton', correct_answer: 'Buxton', answer_context: "Andy told Red to go to a field near Buxton and there would be something there for him!");
shawshank_quiz_2.questions.create(question_number: 10, question: "What was the name of the store that Red and Brooks bagged groceries at?", answer_option_a: 'Food Lion', answer_option_b: 'Food Way', answer_option_c: 'Food Mart', answer_option_d: 'Food Shop', correct_answer: 'Food Way', answer_context: "Both Red and Brooks had jobs bagging groceries at the Food Way!");





